UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications 6000/050 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications
1995-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 10
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/050 PUBS
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Publications.
7101462
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 17, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/024: UNITE Local 23-25 Records 6000/024 AV: UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 MB: UNITE Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 PUBS: UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/050: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files 6000/050 AV: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/050 MB: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050 P: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Organizaiton; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 10 (New York, N.Y.); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees.; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7101462
- UNITE! Stewards Handbook (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Manual del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Manual del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 5: Manual del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Manual del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Stop Sweatshops
    Format: Publication
  - Item 8: Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Safety & Health Checklist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
- UNITE! Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: El embuste del libre comercio
  - Item 2: Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: No a los talleres de explotacion
  - Item 4: Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Temas de Lucha, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- UNITE! Safety and Health Checklist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Safety & Health Checklist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Safety & Health Checklist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Safety & Health Checklist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Non-UNITE! Pamplets, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Health Benefits Under the consolidated Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Questions & Answers: Recent Changes in Health Care Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Everything you need to know to stop NAFTA expansion, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: November
  - Item 4: CAFTA and Free Trade, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Greg Spotts
- UNITE! Pamphlets, 1995-2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 1, Spring/Summer
  - Item 2: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Magnet, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 1, Winter
  - Item 4: Moving Forward Together, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: June 30
  - Item 5: Moving forward Together, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Convention
  - Item 6: Voice, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 61, No. 2, Spring
  - Item 7: Voice, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 61, No. 3, Autumun
  - Item 8: voice, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 62, No. 1, Winter
  - Item 9: voice, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Vol. 63, No. 1, Spring
- UNITE! Local 23-25, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Language: Chinese.
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 52, No. 1, Spring/Summer
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 52, No. 1, Spring/summer
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Noticiero 23-25, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 52, No. 2
  - Item 9: Local 23-25, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 52, No. 2, Autumn
  - Item 10: Local 23-25, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Local 23-25, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Local 23-25, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Local 23-25, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Vol. 46, No. 1, January
- UNITE! Local 23-25, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 50, No.2, Summer
  - Item 2: Local 23-25, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 50, No. 3, Autumn/Winter
  - Item 3: Local 23-25, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 50, No. 3, Autumn/Winter
  - Item 4: Local 23-25, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Local 23-25, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Local 23-25, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Local 23-25, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 51, No. 1
  - Item 8: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 51, No. 1, Spring
  - Item 9: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Local 23-25, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 51, No. 2 Autumn
  - Item 11: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. 51, No. 2, autumn
  - Item 12: Local 23-25, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- UNITE! Local 23-25, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 47, No. 4, October
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 48, No. 1, January
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 48, No. 2, April
  - Item 6: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 48, No. 3, July
  - Item 8: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: July
  - Item 9: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 48, No. 4, Autumn
  - Item 10: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: December
  - Item 11: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 49, No. 1, Winter/Spring
  - Item 12: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 49, No. 1, Winter/spring
  - Item 13: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Winter/Spring
  - Item 14: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 49, No. 2, spring/Summer
  - Item 15: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 49, No. 4, Autumn/Winter
  - Item 17: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Language: chinese.
  - Item 18: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 50, No. 1, Winter
  - Item 19: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: March
- UNITE! Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 46, No. 2, April
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 46, No. 3, July
  - Item 6: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 46, No. 4, October
  - Item 10: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 47, No. 1, January
  - Item 13: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 47, No. 2, April
  - Item 15: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 47, No. 3, July
  - Item 17: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
- UNITE! Ergonomica, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Pongale Un Fin Al Dolor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Ergo Que?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: My Job Is A Pain In The!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- UNITE! Resolutions, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Resolutions, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Miami Beach, July
- UNITE! Product Directory, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Product Directory, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: Second Edition, January
- UNITE! First Constitutional Convention Report, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Executive Board, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- UNITE! Magazine, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Building UNITE-2002 In Review, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: Winter, Vol. 8, No. 4
  - Item 2: Victory at Brylane, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: Spring, Vol. 9, No. 1
  - Item 3: Victory at Brylane, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Victory at Brylane, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Convention delegates chart, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 3, Fall
  - Item 6: Convention delegates chart, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Los delegados a la Convencion trazan, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 3, October
- Garment Industry Daycare Center of Chinatown Fundraising Reception, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Fundraising Reception, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: February 14
  - Item 2: Fundraising Reception, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Feb 14
  - Item 3: Fundraising Reception, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown Fundraising Reception, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Fundraising Reception, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: September 29
  - Item 2: Fundraising Reception, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Fundraising Reception, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Garment Industry Daycare Center of Chinatown Eleventh Anniversary, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Eleventh Anniversary, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: November 2
  - Item 2: Eleventh Anniversary, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Eleventh Anniversary, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- UNITE! Pamphlets, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: NY Metro Area Joint Board, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: NY Metro Area Joint Board, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: NY Metro Area Joint Board, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Unemployment Insurance Telephone Claims Center, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Author: Pataki, George
  - Item 5: Unemployment Insurance Telephone Claims Center, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Unemployment Insurance Telephone Claims Center, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Welcome to Unite!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown Anniversaries, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Seventh Anniversary, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 20
  - Item 2: Unemployment Insurance Telephone Claims Center, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 8
  - Item 3: Fourth Anniversary, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 16
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown Tenth Anniversary, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: 10th Anniversary, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: 10th Anniversary, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: 10th Anniversary, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)